[
  {
    "question": "1kg=______lbs   ?",
    "option": [3, 1.8, 2, 2.2],
    "answer": 2.2,
    "number": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of OOPs   ?",
    "option": [
      "Object oriented file",
      "Omega oriented Programming",
      "Object Omega Programming",
      "Object Oriented Programming"
    ],
    "answer": "Object Oriented Programming",
    "number": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill the article in sentence “I reads in __ MBA   ?",
    "option": ["A", "The", "None of the Above ", "An"],
    "answer": "An",
    "number": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of OOPs   ?",
    "option": [
      "Object oriented file",
      "Omega oriented Programming",
      "Object Omega Programming",
      "Object Oriented Programming"
    ],
    "answer": "Object Oriented Programming",
    "number": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill the article in sentence “I reads in __ MBA   ?",
    "option": ["A", "The", "None of the Above ", "An"],
    "answer": "An",
    "number": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "1kg=______lbs   ?",
    "option": [3, 1.8, 2, 2.2],
    "answer": 2.2,
    "number": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of OOPs   ?",
    "option": [
      "Object oriented file",
      "Omega oriented Programming",
      "Object Omega Programming",
      "Object Oriented Programming"
    ],
    "answer": "Object Oriented Programming",
    "number": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill the article in sentence “I reads in __ MBA   ?",
    "option": ["A", "The", "None of the Above ", "An"],
    "answer": "An",
    "number": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "1kg=______lbs   ?",
    "option": [3, 1.8, 2, 2.2],
    "answer": 2.2,
    "number": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill the article in sentence “I reads in __ MBA   ?",
    "option": ["A", "The", "None of the Above ", "An"],
    "answer": "An",
    "number": 10
  }
]
